{
    "id": "319cba31d07c4a54866cc133b481e51b",
    "title": "Prepositions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "He has done a lot …………………………. me.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "for",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "cac8688e45254628a1540a89ce9c7ce6"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have had a word …………………………… my boss.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "from",
                "with",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a0b6f94ce3dc4d298cdce7d91f90dbdb"
        },
        {
            "question": "We have known each other ……………………………. our school days.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "from",
                "since",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d584652ceefd46a69959c7f36453b116"
        },
        {
            "question": "I am spending the weekend …………………………….. my grandparents.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "with",
                "by"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "255147a3168e4197b8fb5b4a5283257a"
        },
        {
            "question": "You have to start coming ………………………… time.",
            "description": "To come on time is to be neither early nor late. ",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "at",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "c016cbf4bf9f4485ba31ee5942f91765"
        },
        {
            "question": "Dogs must be kept ………………………… a lead.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "on",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ff36c9b564454eeda1a0ac493a89b37c"
        },
        {
            "question": "Do you enjoy living …………………………… the mountains?",
            "description": "The correct expression is in the hills / mountains.",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "in",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "bd288c6dd5014212a9dd6bccd1a84ae5"
        },
        {
            "question": "Do you mind if I look ……………………………… your paper?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "on",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "39586634e77c4aedbe0c8edcbdd72474"
        },
        {
            "question": "The missing girl was found ………………………….. her friend’s house.",
            "description": "At shows position at a point.",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "on",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "4313da2b656a477aae7f5e3e1315db4b"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have heard ………………………………. him but we have never met each other.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "from",
                "with",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "db6c8582efde4143be13e5e710689140"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………………….. having a headache, I enjoyed the picnic.",
            "description": "You can use despite or in spite of here.",
            "answers": [
                "In spite of",
                "Because of",
                "Despite of"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "4d7776b9e1804ebbbbb5bf2088d40b2a"
        },
        {
            "question": "She has been working here …………………………. July.",
            "description": "Since indicates the starting point. It is common with the present perfect or present perfect continuous tense. ",
            "answers": [
                "from",
                "for",
                "since"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "0b53050ba39d4698b5fadcccebf695bd"
        }
    ]
}